gomockingbird.com 2016-04-13

# Privacy | Mockingbird

Some Character LLC. (“Some Character”) operates GoMockingbird.com ("Mockingbird"). It is Some Character’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating Mockingbird.

#### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Some Character collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Mockingbird’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Mockingbird’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Some Character may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Some Character also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Some Character does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

#### Information Gathering

We ask visitors who sign up for an account to provide a valid e-mail address. Those who engage in transactions with Mockingbird – by purchasing premium Mockingbird accounts, for example – are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Some Character collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Mockingbird. Some Character does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

#### Aggregated Statistics

Some Character may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Some Character may monitor the types of widgets most used in mockups made by visitors. Some Character may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Some Character does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

#### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Some Character discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Some Character’s behalf or to provide services available at Some Character’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some Character will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone, except in the following cases: 

  * when required to do so by law
  * or when Some Character believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Some Character, third parties or the public at large.

If you are a registered user of Mockingbird and have supplied your email address, Some Character may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Mockingbird and our products. We expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Some Character takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

#### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Some Character uses cookies to help Some Character identify and track visitors, their usage of Mockingbird’s website, and their website access preferences. Mockingbird visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers may set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Mockingbird, with the drawback that certain features of Mockingbird’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

#### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Some Character may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Some Character’s sole discretion. Some Character encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
